I know you don't realize this, so I'm going to tell you.
うえはら (上原)お前 気づいてないみたいだから言うけど
Since we moved in here...
ここに引っ越してきた日から.
I...
俺...
have...
お前に…
been driven crazy by your antics.
振り回されっぱなしだよな
Huh?
(菜緒)あ...
You make a mess of this place, and get me involved in a catfight.
(上原)部屋は散らかすし
And we even have to pretend like we're dating.
付き合ってるフリまでして
On Christmas you came down with a fever and were bedridden.
クリスマスには熱出して ぶっ倒れるし
I'm sorry.
すいませんでした
And what's more, you caused a blackout on New Year's Eve.
揚げ句大みそかには 停電まで起こすし
Now wait a minute here. I don't have that kind of power--
あのねいくらなんでも 私にそんな力はないから
Trouble just seems to follow you.
嵐を呼ぶ女だよな
Fine, say what you like.
もう何とでも言えば
But, you know...
でもまあ…
it's been a lot of fun.
結構面白い
Huh?
え
That's all I have to say.
だからまあそういうこと
Does that mean...
(菜緒)それってさ
that you enjoy being with me?
私と一緒にいたら 楽しいってこと?
Oh! Could this mean...
あつもしかして
-you actually want us to be a couple? -Hey.
私と本当は付き合いたいってこと? こいつ (上原)おい
Just kidding.
(菜緒)冗談です (上原)お前が寮に移るまでは
I don't mind you living here.
ここでいいかなって よつ 思ってるってこと
There must be some kind of mistake.
これって 何かの間違いじゃない?
How dare you say something like that.
いっせい (一星)失礼なこと言うな
They're lining up because they want a taste of our ramen.
みんなうちのラーメン食べたさに なつ 並 てんだよ
But why all of a sudden?
(菜緒)なぜ突然?
This.
(一星) これ
"Spring date spot special report."
"新春デートスポット特集" 谷テ
I see.
ふー ん
Wow!
おお
Huh? Issei?
え?いっちゃん?
That writer is one of our long-time customers.
(一星)その雑誌のライターさんがさ うちの昔からのなじみ客で
I see.
ふー ん
Since that article came out couples have been lining up like that.
(一星)その雑誌に出てから カップルがこのとおり
-There's a coupon in there too. -Really?
しかも割引券付きだからな (菜緒)へえー
A ramen date sounds kind of nice.
何かいいな ラーメンデートって
Really? Don't women want something fancier,
(徹平)そうかい? 女の子はもっとシャレた
like French or Italian food?
フレンチとかイタ飯とか 行きたいんじゃないのかい?
That's exactly why they like this.
だからこそですよ
Here you can spend time together in a more casual way.
2人が気取らない関係って感じ?
I wish I had someone to eat ramen with.
憧れるなあ ラーメン食べる仲って
But I think that a man's true feelings are for the ramen.
まあ確かに 男の本音はラーメンだろうな
But doesn't eating together mean
(菜緒) でも一緒に食べるってことは
that you can tell each other your true feelings?
本音で言い合えるってことでしょ (徹平)なるほどねえ
Man-woman relationships can be very deep.
深いねえ男女の仲ってのは
Nao, why don't you come here for your next date?
よしかわ 吉川もさ今度食べ来いよ デートで
Here.
はい
If you don't have anyone, I'll eat with you if you like.
まあ相手いなかったら 一緒に食ってやってもいいけど
A date...
デートかぁ
Today marks the start of third trimester.
(校長)-今日から 3学期が始まるわけですが
Seniors must face entrance exams...
3年生は受験シーズン 本番を迎え…
Aw, jeez. School's already started.
(まりな) あ~あついに始まったのねえ
I had so many remedial lessons, I don't feel rested at all.
(菜緒)何か補習ばっかで 全然休んだ気しないよ
Oh! From tomorrow I've got to get up earlier to make lunch.
あっ明日から早起きして お弁当作んなきゃだ
Just buy one at the canteen. It's a lot easier.
(光石)無理しないで 購買で買えばいいじゃん
That's far too wasteful, Mitsuishi.
甘いよみつちゃん!
It's way cheaper to make one yourself.
作ったほうが ずっと安上がりなんだよ
This trimester I made up my mind to make my own lunch.
私新学期からちゃんと お弁当作るの決めたから
Then why don't you make enough for Uehara as well?
じゃあ上原君の分も ついでに作ればいいじゃん
What?
え?
If you're making one, you might as well make enough for two.
まりな)どうせ作るなら 1つも2つも同じでしょ
Then you can eat together too!
何なら一緒に 可なら 食べればいいじゃん!
Lunch with Uehara?
上原君とお弁当?
Nah, that'll never happen.
あ...ないない
Since you're supposed to be dating, eating together won't seem strange.
付き合ってることに なつてるんだから
Yep. If you're dating, that is.
(光石) うんまあ 付き合ってるならな
-You can say, "Open wide!" -Yeah, "Open wide!"
(まりな) あ んとかしちゃつたりして つに (光石)あ~んとか
No way.
やだあ
Uehara would never eat with me.
上原君が私と 食べてくれるわけないもん
Sure.
仩原)いいよ (菜緒)え?
-You're going to make lunch for me, right? -Uh-huh. I will.
だって弁当作ってくれんだろ (菜緒) うん作る
Then I'd totally eat it. Let's eat together.
食うよ全然 緒に食う
-Really? -Uh-huh.
本当に? 仩原) うん
Besides, I'm always hungry.
俺いつでも腹減ってるし
Yeah, you're right.
だよね~
Hey!
あっちよつと
-Good morning.
(菜緒)よいしょおはよう まりな)おはよう
-How many days is that for? -And how many people?
ってか何日分? (光石)何人分?
Uehara is a big eater.
上原君って大食いなんだよ
Yeah, but even so... Well, whatever.
いや…にしてもさ まあいいや
-Now listen to me, Nao. -Huh?
いい?菜緒 (菜緒)ん?
You must really play the part of a lovey-dovey couple well.
上原君と思いっきり ラブラブな恋人を演じるの
-Lovey-dovey? -Why?
ラブラブ? (光石)なぜ?
The reason why so many actors in dramas become couples
まりな) ドラマで共演した俳優さんが カップルになりやすいのは
is because they're playing the part of being a couple!
疑似恋愛するからだって こつ いうじゃん!
-Is that true? -Nah, that's impossible.
そうなの? (光石)いや無理あるでしょ
-Shut up, Mitsuishi. -Yes, ma'am.
みつちゃんは黙る! (光石)はい
Get this, Nao.
だからね菜緒
If you and Uehara play being sweethearts, then someday you really will become one.
菜緒も上原君と恋人を演じれば いつか本当に恋人になれるから!
Understand?
分かった?
Yes... I'll try my best.
はいはい… 頑張ります
Of course if this will eventually get him to like me, then I want to try.
そりゃ両想いになれるもんなら なりたいさ
But how should we play the role of being sweethearts.
でも恋人を演じるって 何すりゃいいんだか
-Here. Open wide. -Ahh.
はいあ~ん (上原)あ~ん
Yum. It's delicious.
うんおいしい
No way. Never. That'll never happen.
いやいや… それは無理でしょ
-That's her, Uehara's girl. -Really?
(女子生徒)あの人だよ上原君の (女子生徒)へえー
-She's pretty cute, isn't she? -Who? Who?
結構かわいい人じゃん (女子生徒)どの子?どの子?
-That girl sitting over there. -Really?
(女子生徒)あそこに座ってる女の子 (女子生徒)へえー
-She's cute, huh? -Yeah, she is.
(女子生徒)かわいくない? (女子生徒)かわいいね
Yeah, she is pretty cute.
(女子生徒)本当だ 結構かわいいね
Uh-huh, she sure is.
(女子生徒) うんかわいいよね
Oh, that's right!
そうだ そうだよ!
Here at school, I'm Uehara's girlfriend.
私学校では 上原君の彼女じゃん!
What are you doing?
(上原)何してんだよ
-Oh, Uehara. -Hurry up and let's eat.
あっ上原君 (上原) さっさと食うぞ
Okay.
(菜緒)はい
Let's dig in.
いただきます
I can do this.
よし
Here, say ahh...
はいあ~ん
-Come on! Here! Open wide. -What's with you?
ほれほれ!あ~ん (上原)何のマネだ?
You're the one who said we had to act like we were dating.
だ…だってそっちが 付き合ってるフリしろって言ったから
Nobody does that when they're dating.
しねーよ! 付き合っててもそんなこと!
Yes they do! Look!
してるよあそこ!
-Open wide. -Ahh.
(女子生徒)あ~ん (男子生徒)あ~ん ああ
-Do you like it? -It's delicious.
(女子生徒)おいしい? (男子生徒)おいしい
I knew you'd like it. I worked hard to make it.
でしよ 生懸命作ったんだ で!
-Thank you. -Oh, you have something here.
(男子生徒)ありがとう (女子生徒)あれ?何がついてる
It's rice.
ご飯粒 (男子生徒)やめろよ
-Give that to me. I'll eat it myself. -Oh!
(上原)貸せ自分で食うわ (菜緒)あっ!
What's with him?
何なの…ったく
Thank you very much.
(上原)ごちそうさまでした
Let's do this.
よし!
-Go ahead. -What?
ど…どうぞ (上原)何が?
You don't know? Put your head on my knees.
何がって膝枕
-Nobody does that! -Yes they do!
(上原)するか! (菜緒) してるってば!
There's something wrong with you.
お前変だぞ?
Did you eat something off the street?
何か悪いものでも 拾い食いしたのか?
How rude! Who'd eat off the street?
失礼な 誰が拾い食いなんか
I'm just trying to make it look like
人がせっかく
What? You want us to be lovey-dovey?
(上原)何お前 俺とラブラブしたいの?
That's not what I mean.
そういうんじゃないよ
It's just that since we're supposed to look like a couple,
ただ付き合ってるから そんぐらいしないとかなって よつ
I see.
(上 )ふーん 原
-Oh, forget it. -Forget what?
もういい (上原)何が?
-I'm leaving. -Why?
帰る (上原)はあ?
-Clean this up. -Hey, I haven't eaten...
片付けて (上原)お前フルーツ食って
I haven't eaten the fruits yet. Let me have the fruits!
フルーツ食ってねーだろおい フルーツ食わせろよ
-I'm gonna eat-- -Ah!
(菜緒)私が食べる (菜緒,上原)あー!
You wipe it up, Uehara!
(菜緒)上原君が拭いてよ
You're the one who spilled it.
上原君が今こぼしたんだよね
-I don't have a handkerchief. -I don't either.
(上原)俺ハンカチ持ってないし (菜緒)私だって持ってないもん こつ
You've got that. Wipe with it.
(上原)それあんじゃんか 拭けよ
Hey! That's my fruit!
(菜緒)あっ!私のフルーツ
Stop!
ちよつと! ちょっと!
Give it back!
か…返せ!ねえ!
-How about going for some tea? -Why?
ねえお茶でも行かない? (上原)何で?
Why not?
何でって...
If you want some, then have it at home.
飲みたいなら 家で飲めばいいじゃん
Oh, is that so?
あらそうですか
-Nao! Uehara! -Oh, Yuri!
ひさし (百合)菜緒ちゃん!久志! (菜緒)あーゆりりん!
I was just on my way over to your place.
(百合)今からちょうど 2人のとこへ行こうと思ってたの
Are you off today?
(菜緒)今日仕事お休み?
Kind of. I took off after doing an interview.
佰合) うんちょっと 取材ついでに抜けてきた
-What did you come here for? -Why can't I?
(上原)何しに来たんだよ 佰合)いいじゃん
I came to bring you souvenirs.
お土産届けに来たんだから
-You mean from Hawaii? -That's right.
もしかしてハワイの? 佰刽そう!
-Ta-da! This too. -Wow!
ジャーン!こっちも (菜緒)わあ
I'm going to drop by a friend's, then I'll be home.
俺友達のとこ寄って帰るわ (菜緒)え?
Hey, Uehara.
佰刽ちょっと久志
Bye.
じゃあな
What's with him? He doesn't even have any friends.
何よ友達なんかいないくせに
He's just as unfriendly as ever.
相変わらず愛想ない奴
-This... -Wow!
(百合) これとこれと.
-and this too. -Wow!
あとこれ (菜緒)わあ
Look at all this. Can I really have all of it?
すごい こんなたくさんいいの?
-Sure! -Yes!
佰合)うん! (菜緒)やった
Oh, this bikini...
(百合)あつこの水着
I bought it on a whim, but I don't look good in it.
ノリで買っちゃつたんだけど 私には若すぎて
Why don't you wear it, Nao?
よかったら菜緒ちゃん 着てくれない?
-Really? Can I? -Sure.
えついいの? 佰合) うん
I'm so happy.
(菜緒) うれしい
It's so pretty.
かわいい
But I wonder if the size is all right.
でもサイズ大丈夫かな?
I wish I were like you, Yuri.
ゆりりんはいいなあ
You're so beautiful, with such a nice figure,
美人だしスタイルもよくて 明るくて仕事もできて
I can totally see why Uehara likes you.
上原君が好きになるのも 分かる
Oh, Nao! You flatter me!
菜緒ちゃんったらもう!
But I'm serious. You've got such confidence in yourself.
でも本当に 自分に自信があるっていうかさ
-I don't have confidence in myself. -What?
佰刽自信なんかないよ (菜緒)え?
I'm jealous of you, Nao.
私は菜緒ちゃんが うらやましいけどな
What? Of me?
え?私が?
You're always trying your hardest.
いつも一生懸命って感じで
I was like that before I got married.
私も結婚する前は そんなだったなあ
That may have been the best time of my life.
あの頃が一番楽しかったかも
Anyway, never mind.
なーhKね
But now that you're married, you can always be with the one you love.
でも結婚したら好きな人と ずーっと一緒にいられるじゃん
That's what I thought.
そう思ってたけど
But the closer we are... the more anxiety I feel.
近いほど 不安になることもあるんだよ
I mean, the day we came back from our honeymoon,
新婚旅行から 帰ってきた日だって
Takuya went right to work from the airport.
卓也空港から まっすぐ仕事行っちゃつたしね
-Oh, I'm sorry. I'm just whining. -No.
あーごめん!完全にグチ! 元 (菜緒) ううん
-Let's have some chocolate. -Okay.
チョコ食べよっか (菜緒) うん
Oh, Daichi.
89大ちゃん
-What are these? -I received these complimentary tickets.
(菜緒)何これ? (大地)招待券もらったんだ
You've always liked the aquarium, right?
昔から好きだろ水族館
Yes! I love it!
うん大好き!
-If you're free Sunday, you want to go? -Really?
今度の日曜暇だったら行くか? (菜緒)いいの?
-Yeah. I don't have practice. - Okay, I'll go.
(大地) うん部活もないし (菜緒) うん行く !
Is this what you wanted to talk about the other day?
この前話そうと思ってたことって このこと?
Oh, uh, yeah... You keep the tickets, Nao.
ああ うんまあ チケット菜緒が持ってて
Okay, I will. Thank you, Daichi.
うん分かった ありがとう大ちゃん
-Nao. -Oh, Uehara.
(上原)吉川 (菜緒)あっ上 君 原
-Oh... -Hi.
(大地)あ 仩原)どうも
You're late.
おせーよ
Did you come to get me?
もしかして 迎えに来てくれたの?
No, to get lunch. Break is going to be over soon.
ああ弁当を 昼休み終わっちまうだろ な
-Fine. -Hey!
(菜緒)はいはい (大地)おい しし はお
Is that all you can do after she made that for you?
作ってもらっておいて 何だよその態度
-What's that got to do with you? -What's wrong?
先輩には関係ないでしょ (菜緒)ちょっと
I'm sorry, Daichi.
ごめんな大ちゃん
He gets short tempered when he's hungry.
上原君お腹すくと すぐ気立っちゃうから
Wait up.
ちょっと... ちよつと
-Thank you, Daichi. -No problem.
ありがとね大ちゃん 休地)おう
Daichi...
大地先輩
She sure seems happy even though they're just faking it.
付き合ってるフリなのに あんなに浮かれちゃつて
Are you sure you're okay with things going the way they are?
いいんですか あのまんまにさせとして
Of course not.
いいわけないだろ
I got these from Daichi.
大ちゃんからもらったの
He said he's going to take me to the aquarium this Sunday.
今度の日曜に 連れてってくれるんだって水族館
I haven't been there in awhile.
久々だなあ
-Do you like the aquarium, Uehara? -So, Nao...
上原君も水族館好き? 仩原)吉川ってさ
are you two dating?
あの人と付き合ってんの?
What? No, of course we're not.
え?違うよ そんなわけないじゃん
I see.
(上 )ふーん 原
How could you date a guy you don't even like?
好きでもない奴とデートできる お前の神経疑う
It's not really a date.
別にデートじゃないし
I'd never consider going out with someone if I didn't like them.
俺は好きでもない奴と どっか行きたいとか思わないから
What's that supposed to mean?
何それ
You know you still like Yuri,
上原君だってまだ ゆりりんのこと好きなくせに
but you're living with me, right?
私と一緒に住んでんじゃん
It's not like I wanted to.
それは仕方なくだろ!
You didn't want to...
仕方なく…
Yeah, I guess you're right.
そうだよね
Gee, I'm sorry that I forced you to live with me and eat lunch with me.
好きじゃない人と一緒に住んで お弁当食べて
I'm sorry.
ごめん
I'm done.
(上原)ごちそうさま
He must really be angry.
(菜緒)怒ってるよなあ
Manager, can I have another serving?
(上原)店長 お代わりしてもいいっすか?
Sure, but this is unusual.
(明)ああ構わないけど 珍しいな
You've not been eating much.
ここんとこ そんなに食べてなかったのに
Did you have a fight with that girl?
(ななこ) あの女とケンカでもした?
What on earth am I doing?
何やってんだ私
Aah!
ああー!
What am I going to do?
どうしよう
Didn't you sleep well?
寝不足?
No...
うんちょっとね
-Where's your lunch? -I overslept.
(光石)弁当は? (菜緒)今日寝坊しちゃつて
I see. But you seemed so inspired before.
(まりな)ふーん あんなに気合入ってたのに?
Won't Uehara say anything if you don't have lunch for him?
弁当ないとさ上原君に 何か言われるんじゃないの?
I doubt it.
そんなことないよ
He's probably glad I didn't bring one.
ないならないで 気楽なんじゃない?
Did you have a fight?
(まりな)ケンカでもした?
Okay! I'll buy you anything you want today.
よし!今日は俺が 何でもおごってやる
Yes! Only a doctor's son can do that!
よっ!さすがみつちゃん 医者の息子
Stop saying that.
そういうことばっかりね 言うね
-I can hardly wait. -You too?
ごちそうさまです! (光石)お前も?
-Why? Is there a problem? -No.
えっ何か文句あんの? (光石)大丈夫
-I thought so. -All right.
(まりな)でしょ (光石)たぶん しん
Thanks, you two.
2人ともありがとう
-Let's go. -Okay.
まりな)行こう (菜緒) うん
Here we go.
(まりな)よし
Oh, it's Uehara.
(女子生徒)あっ上原君だ
He's so much better than the other guys.
(女子生徒)やっぱり 他の男子とは違うよね
What a stud!
(女子生徒)かっこいい
-Uehara is buying his lunch again. -I guess they've broken up.
(詩織)上原君が購買に戻ってきた (エリカ)別れたってことかしら
I never thought he'd stick with that girl for very long.
(美南)あんな女と続くなんて 最初から思ってなかったわ
That plain Jane is just not a good match for Uehara.
(詩織)釣り合わないのよ 上原君とあんな普通の女
How could you date a guy you don't even like?
(上原)好きでもない奴と デートできるお前の神経疑う
I'd never consider going out with someone if I didn't like them.
俺は好きでもない奴とは どっか行きたいとか思わないから
What business is this of Uehara's anyway?
上原君には関係ないから
-Good morning, Daichi. -Hi.
(菜緒)おはよう大ちゃん 休地)おう
You didn't forget the tickets, did you?
チケット忘れてないだろうな?
Of course not. I'd never forget.
もちろん 忘れるわけないじゃん
-Okay, let's go. -Yeah.
(大地)よし行こう! (菜緒) うん
I'm looking forward to this.
うーん楽しみだな
-It's been awhile. -Yeah, it has.
久々だね遊びに行くの (大地)なっ よつ
-Look, Nao. Tokyo Tower. -Oh! Look at that.
あっ菜緒東京タワ (菜緒)あっ本当だ
-It's close. -We're so close to it.
(大地)近いな (菜緒)近~い
-Wow! -Jelly fish.
(菜緒)わあ (大地)クラゲだ
Aren't they amazing, Daichi?
すごい ねえ大ちゃん い大
Yeah.
おう
Oh, wow!
わあ
Look at these, Daichi.
ねえ大ちゃん見て
Wow! They're so cute. Look how small they are.
すごーいかわいいね ほらちっちゃい
So cute.
かわいい
Huh?
(菜緒)あれ?
-Oh, no. -What's wrong?
え? ス 休地どうした?
I can't find my phone.
(菜緒)携帯がない
-Really? Did you lose it? -Where is it?
(大地) マジ?どっか落とした?
It's probably at home.
(菜緒)たぶんうちだ
Besides, we were able to meet up okay.
こうやって待ち合わせも 会えてるわけだし
I'll take photos for us.
写真なら俺ので撮るよ
-Good idea. Let's go. -Yeah.
そうだね 行こっか 休地)おう
-They're cute. -They sure are.
(大地)かわいいな (菜緒)ねつかわいい
-Look how big their tummies are. -Their feathers look so soft.
お腹すごい膨らんでる (大地)ねえ毛柔らかそう
-Oh, capybara. -Look, capybara.
(菜緒)えつカピバラだ (大地)カピバラだ
They're just standing still.
止まってる
Nao, isn't that a turtle?
菜緒カメじゃない?
-Really? Where? -There.
(菜緒)えっどこ? 休地ほら
-It says, "Touch here." -It's a touch screen.
(大地) "触ってみよう! " (菜緒)タッチパネルじゃん
-Oh, what's this? -Wow!
(大地)のお一何か出てきた (菜緒) うわっ
-Which one? -Sunfish.
何する? (大地)マンボウ
Okay, sunfish.
(菜緒)マンボウ 小
Look, look! It's spinning around. Amazing!
見て見て見てグルグル回る すごい
It sure is.
(大地) あ な
She forgot this.
忘れ物ですよ
-Oh! Take a picture. -Sure thing.
(菜緒)あっ!ねえ写真撮って (大地)あいよ
-Send it right away. -Now?
(菜緒)すぐ送ってね (大地)今? A?
You always forget, Daichi.
(菜緒)だって大ちゃん こつ すぐ忘れんじゃん
-Okay, okay. -We'll take a photo for you.
(大地)はいはい (従業員)一緒にお撮りしますよ
How about a souvenir of your date? $5 per photo.
デートの記念にいかがですか? 1枚500円です
But this isn't really a date--
(菜緒)そんな デートってわけじゃない…
-Yes, I'd like one. -What? You want one?
お願いします (菜緒)えっ撮るの?
-What a waste of $5. -I don't mind.
500円もったいないよ (大地)いいから
-Take one with this too, please. -Certainly.
これもお願いします (従業員)はい
-Look at the camera, please. -Say "Cheese."
(従業員) こっち向いてくださ-い (従業員)はいチーズ!
Oh, no.
3 to
They're so big.
(菜緒)おっきい
Nao.
(大地)菜緒 (菜緒)ん?
Are you really looking for a place to move to?
(大地)引っ越し先 ちゃんと探してるのか?
To be honest, I'm against you living with Uehara.
上原と同居って 俺はやっぱちょっと反対だよ
-Daichi... -Even though you say it's all right,
大ちゃん
he's still a guy.
あいつも年頃の男なわけだし
I mean, if something does happen, then it'll be too late.
何かあってからじゃ 遅いっていうか
Your parents don't know about it either, right?
おばさんたちにも 内緒なんだろ?
Thank you for worrying about me.
心配してくれてありがとう
But there's no need to worry.
でも安心して
There's already someone in his life...
上原君には ちゃんと好きな人いるから
Then why do you make him lunch every day?
(大地) じゃあお前 何のために毎日弁当作ってんだよ
Well, you see...
それは 付き合ってるフリするため
so nobody finds out we're living together.
同居バレないように?
You like Uehara, don't you?
菜緒は上原のことが 好きなんだろ?
If you really do like him,
(大地)本当に好きなのに
why do you pretend that you're dating?
付き合ってるフリして 毎日弁当作って
Why do you let him treat you like that, when you make his lunch everyday?
であんな態度取られて
He even likes someone else.
向こうには好きな奴がいてさ
Is that really what you want?
お前本当にそれでいいのか
But I just can't help it.
(菜緒)だって仕方ないじゃん
I like him.
好きなんだもん
So, I don't mind.
だからもういいの
As long as I can be with him.
そばにいられればそれだけで
Maybe, someday...
もしかしたら いつか私も
he'll come to find me attractive.
少しは女として 見てもらえるかもしれないじゃん?
His feelings just might change, you know.
人の気持ちなんて 変わるかもしれないし
Yeah, I guess so.
そうだな
Uh-huh.
うん
-Then I still have hope. -What?
なら俺も希望が持てる (菜緒)ん?
I like you.
好きだよ
I like you, Nao.
俺菜緒のことが好き
Oh, Daichi. Stop joking around.
大ちゃんそういう冗談やめて
It's the truth.
本当
I've always liked you, Nao.
俺ずっと前から 菜緒のことが好き
I always thought it was enough if you just smiled at me.
菜緒が笑ってればいいやとか 思ってたけど
But I'm done thinking like that.
もうそういうのやめた
I don't think that anymore.
やめたんだ
-Daichi-- -You don't have to...
大ちゃん (大地)今は
give me an answer now.
返事はいらない
I just wanted to tell you.
ただ言いたかっただけ こかつたに
-Can I keep this? -Why?
これもらっていい? (菜緒)え?
To commemorate our first date.
初デートの記念
Can you get back home alone?
菜緒1人で帰れるか?
Yes.
(菜緒) うん
Sorry... but I have to leave now.
悪い… 俺先帰るわ
Daichi!
(菜緒)大ちゃん!
I'm looking for someone.
(上原)あの… 人を探してほしいんですけども
I see. Did you lose someone?
(受付係)では迷子ということで よろしいですか?
Yes, I guess you could say that.
まあそんなもんですね
May I have the name and age.
(受付係) お名前と年齢をお願いします
Her name is Nao Yoshikawa. She's seven... teen.
(上原)名前は吉川菜緒 10... 7?
-Nao Yoshikawa. She's 10? Seven? -Yes.
吉川なおちゃん 10歳? 7歳?
-No, 17. -Seventeen that is.
あついや17 (受付係) 17
Seventy.
(上原)セブンティーン
-Seventeen. -Yes.
セブンティーン (上原)ええ
Uehara!
(菜緒)上原君!?
Nao.
EHJII
What are you doing?
何してんの?
That's what I should be asking you.
お前こっちのセリフだよ
This has been ringing all morning, so I brought it for you.
これ朝から鳴り続けてたから 持ってきてやったんだよ つにんに
Really? You went through all that trouble?
え?わざわざ?
It's just that it might be an emergency.
いや何か緊急の用だったら 困んだろ
Thank you.
ありがとう
Wow! Look at all these calls.
うわつ こんなたくさん
Sorry, this will take a second.
ごめんちょっといい?
Hi, Mom? Is something wrong?
もしもしお母さん? 何かあったの?
Oh, Nao. It's nothing. I figured it out.
(美紀子)ああ菜緒ごめん 何でもない解決したわ
What?
え?
I didn't know how to use the DVR so I was going to ask you.
(美紀子)テレビの録画やり方が 分かんないから聞こうと思って 田
That's all it was? Stop worrying me like that.
それだけ? もうびっくりさせないでよね
Okay, okay. I'm busy, so I've got to go.
(美紀子)はいはい じゃあ忙しいから切るわよ!
What?
あっちよつ…
Darn her.
もう何なの
Sorry. It was completely trivial.
ごめん くだらないことだった
No, it's okay. It's my fault for panicking over it.
仩原)いや別に 俺が勝手に焦っただけだから
Hey... why are you all alone?
つ-かお前何で1人?
Daichi already went home.
大ちゃん先に帰ったから
I see.
(上 )ふーん 原
-Nao. -Yes?
仩原)吉川 (菜緒)ん? 吉ん )ノ)ノ 上菜
Wow!
うわあ
It's so pretty.
きれい
You know what?
(菜緒)今日ね
Today was just like you said. It was a date.
上原君の言うとおり デートだった こつに
So you finally figured that out?
何を今さら
You're really slow.
お前本当にアホだな
Hey...
ちょっ... ちよつ…
Dim-witted, clumsy and forgetful.
(上原)鈍いしドジだし 忘れっぽいし
How can you call me dim-witted?
上原君に鈍いって 言われたくないんだけど!
-Dim-wit, dim-wit, dim-wit-- -You're so mean!
(LR)鈍い鈍い鈍い... (菜緒)ひどい!
You're dim-witted, cruel and... you eat too much!
上原君だって鈍いし意地悪だし こつ あと…大食いじゃん
Oh dear!
(菜緒)えっ! 仩原)ハハハ…
-You want to get something to eat? -Huh?
何か食いに行くか (菜緒)え?
-But it's right before payday. -Me too.
つっても俺給料日前 蝌日前 (菜緒)私も
Oh, right.
あつ
What's this?
(EIA)
-Here you go. -Oh, it looks delicious.
(一星)はいお待ち (上原)おおーうまそー!
-Let's eat.
いただきます (菜緒)いただきます
It's great.
(上原)あつうまい!
Thanks.
そうか! (上原)お前何で
Hey, are you keeping it a secret?
えっ何でお前 秘密にしてんだよ?
-It's just that... -See how great she looks.
だって につて (一星) こんなに似合ってんのに
Hey! Don't!
(菜緒)ちょっ...いっちゃん 仩原)ギャハハハ…!
It suits her perfectly.
似合いすぎだろこれ
-Yeah, it does. -Issei! No, it doesn't!
(菜緒)いっちゃん… (一星)似合ってる
Give it back!
返してよ!
-This is totally hilarious. -No, it's not. Cut it out.
(上原)アゴ外れてん ゃん (菜緒)外れてないからあるもん じ
Give it here.
返してよ
-Let me help. -It's okay, Nao.
手伝います (徹平)いいんだよ菜緒ちゃん
Today you're a customer.
今日はお客さんなんだから
Okay, thank you for the good meal.
じゃあごちそうさまです
-I'm happy for you. -About what?
よかったじゃねえか (菜緒)ん?
You said you wanted to have a ramen date, right?
デートでラーメン食べるってのに 憧れてたんだろ?
No, that wasn't a date.
いやデートってわけじゃ ないですから
Don't be shy.
照れんなよ!
I can pretty much tell by the way a man eats.
俺はね食べっぷり見てれば 大体分かるんだよ るんに
Whether he's is a good guy or not.
そいつがいい男かどうか
He's a real nice one!
なかなかのいい男じゃねえか!
I'm serious. It wasn't a date.
(菜緒)本当に違いますから
Who could that be?
誰だろ
Yes?
はーい
-Daichi. -Good morning.
大ちゃん (大地)おはよ
Let's go to school together. I want to talk to you about something.
一緒に学校行こう 少し話したいんだ
Okay.
(菜緒) うん
I'm sorry about leaving you yesterday.
(大地)昨日ごめんな 先に帰って
-It's okay. -I wanted to apologize.
(菜緒) ううん (大地)謝りたくてさ んた うり
But I have no intention of apologizing for saying that I like you.
でも好きだって言ったことは 謝るつもりないから
Huh?
え?
I just wanted to say it
言いたかっただけって 言ったけど
and I don't want to take it back.
なかったことに したいわけじゃないから
Daichi, I--
大ちゃん私
I told you, you don't have to give me an answer.
言っただろ? つたたク 返事はいらないって
You're the one who said a person's feelings might change, right?
人の気持ち変わるかもしれないって 言ったのは菜緒だろ?
But that was about...
あれは…
I'm going to become the kind of guy you're attracted to.
俺勝手に頑張るから 菜緒に男として見てもらえるように
I'm no longer going to play the older brother role.
幼なじみのお兄ちゃんは もう卒業
That's all I wanted to say. I've got to get to morning practice.
言いたかったのはそれだけ 俺もう朝練行くわ
-Want to ride on back? -What?
後ろ乗るか? (菜緒)えっ!
No, I'm not.
し…してないよ! (大地)ハハッじゃあな
I mean, I heard they broke up.
(敦子)だって別れたらしいよ
They haven't had lunch together in a while either.
(桜) ここ最近 ずっとお昼も一緒じゃないし
And I heard that today Nao came to school with Daichi.
(敦子)今日吉川さん 大地先輩と一緒に来てたらしいよ
Seriously? She sure bounced back fast.
(絵梨菜)マジ!? 切り替え早すぎじゃん
Hey, hey! Listen up! This is just crazy.
(エリカ)ねえねえ…注目注目 ヤバいヤバいヤバい
-I heard Uehara and Nao broke up. -No way! Why?
上原君と吉川さんって別れたんだって こんにつ (静香)ウソ!何で?
Oh, yeah. I heard they had a big fight.
(美南)あつそういえば 何か大ゲンカしたとかって
No, they said Uehara grew tired of Nao.
違くて上原君が 吉川さんに飽きて振ったんだって つにんにつ
Good morning, Uehara.
おはよう上原君
Morning.
おはよう
Did you make up with Uehara?
(まりな) 上原君とは仲直りできたの?
Yeah, I think so.
(菜緒) うんたぶん
Then why didn't you bring lunch?
じゃあ何で 弁当じゃないんだよ
I couldn't go shopping yesterday.
昨日はちょっと 買い物できなかったから
Uehara, is it true you and Nao broke up?
(元樹) 上原吉川と別れたって本当?
No.
いや
Then how come she hasn't brought you lunch?
(元樹) じゃあ何で 愛妻弁当じゃなくなったわけ?
Oh, I'm not sure.
(上原)ああそれはちょっとね
If you haven't broken up, you should tell everyone.
(元樹)別れてないなら みんなにそう言わないと
-It only hurts Nao if you don't. -What am I supposed to say?
吉川さんかわいそうじゃん (LR)誰に何を言えっての?
I mean, there's all kinds of crazy rumors flying around.
だって何か こつ いろいろ変な噂立ってるし
Rumors?
噂?
Like you got sick of her and dumped her.
お前が吉川さんに 飽きて捨てたとか
Or that she was playing you for a fool.
吉川さんのほうがお前を もてあそんだとか
And then there's one that she was two-timing you with Daichi.
あと吉川さんが篠崎先輩とお前に 二股かけてたとか
Nao.
(詩織)吉川さん
Yes?
はい
We're here to find out the truth.
(詩織)事実確認したいんだけど
Is it true you broke up with Uehara?
(エリカ)あんた 上原君と別れたって本当?
-Well... -We want a clear answer.
(菜緒)それは (美南)はっきりしたいんだけど
You don't want any more rumors about you going around,
あなただって "二股かけた"とか
like you're a two-timer or that kind of thing, right?
そんな噂これ以上 立てられたくないでしょ
-I'm going to get Uehara. -Wait.
私上原君呼んでくる (光石)待てよ
But all these awful rumors make it sound like she's to blame.
だって菜緒ばっか悪者で 変な噂立てられてんのに
Why would you want to stay out of it? How dare you!
放つておくってどういうことなの? 許せない!
But it's not Uehara that's spreading the rumors.
(光石)でも上原君が 噂流してるわけじゃないだろ
But since Uehara's involved, these kinds of rumors spread.
相手が上原君だから こういう噂が立つんでしょ!
Let go!
離してよ
Nao.
上原)吉川 仩原)吉川
Oh, Uehara.
あっ上原君
I came to get you.
迎えに来た
Huh?
え?
Let's walk home together.
緒に帰ろう
I'll take your bag.
(上原)荷物
Let's go.
行くぞ
Sorry.
(上原)ごめん
I guess a lot of bad rumors got started.
何か変 噂 立てられてたみたいで な
I didn't know it was going on.
俺気づかなくてさ
It's all right. I'm used to it.
平気平気 こういうの慣れてるし
You're used to it?
慣れてるって
-I'm the one who should apologize. -Why?
私のほうこそごめん (上原)何が?
Because I said a pretty callous thing to you about Yuri.
この前ゆりりんのこと 無神経なこと言って
I should have apologized earlier, but so many things were happening...
謝んなきゃって思ってたんだけど いろいろあって
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
After you said that to me about Yuri,
俺が百合のこと言われて
the reason I couldn't face you,
お前と顔合わせないように してたのは
was simply because I was embarrassed.
単に恥ずかしかったからで
That's not the kind of thing
別にそんなことで
that would get me angry at you,
吉川のこと怒ったり 女又 傷ついたりもしないし
Besides, I've gotten over her.
ってかもう吹っ切れてるし
You don't need to worry about it.
そんな気使わなくていいからさ
Really?
え
Oh, I don't want to talk about this stuff.
あーもうこの話やめやめ!
Listen. Don't ever talk about this again.
いいか もうこの話はすんなよ つしのロ
-But-- -I said, "Don't."
でも (上原)するなって! よつ
-Okay, here we go. -Oh, oh, oh.
はいお待たせー 仩厕858585
There.
(菜緒) よいしょ
-Ready? -Yeah.
いくよ 仩原)おう
-Ta-da. -Wow! It looks delicious.
(菜緒)ジャーン (上原)おおうまそー!
-Thank you for the meal. -Okay.
いただきます (菜緒)はーい
-Let's eat. -This is great today.
(上原)すごいな今日
-There's so much. -Yeah, there's a lot.
豪華だな (菜緒)豪華でしょ
I put a lot in.
いっぱい入れたんだ
-Look at the carrots. -Oh, wow.
ねえニンジン見て (上原)本当だ
It took me an hour to cut them like that.
(菜緒) くり抜いたの 1時間もかけて
That's way too long.
(上原)かかりすぎだろ
Yum. This is good.
うんうまい
What's with you? Quit staring.
何だよ気持ち悪い
I can't help it. It's been awhile since we ate together.
だって久々じゃん こつ 緒にご飯食べるの
Oh, chicken. I don't have any chicken.
あっ鶏肉 鶏肉取ってない
I'll give you a meatball.
団子あげるよ
I've got meatballs. I got a lot of them.
仩原)団子取ったの いっぱい取ったの団子は
-Have more meatballs. -I've got plenty.
団子食べなよ (上原)団子はいっぱい取ったんだよ
The meatballs are more expensive.
(菜緒)団子のほうが高いの
Yum. I'm going to have some chicken.
うーん鶏肉食べよ
I think it's raining.
(上原)降ってきたな
-You're right. -Yeah.
(菜緒)本当だね 仩原) うん
I knew something weird would happen since you're making dinner.
お前が料理作るから 何か変だと思ったら
What? Why is it my fault?
(菜緒)何が? 何私のせいにしてんの?
-Huh?
仩原)ん? (菜緒)ん?
Who could that be?
誰だろ
Yes?
はーい
Yuri!
(菜緒)ゆりりん!?
What's wrong? You're soaking wet.
どうしたの?ゆりりん びしょ濡れだよ
Yuri.
(上原)百合!
What happened to you?
どうしたんだよ
Uehara...
久志…
I'm getting a divorce.
私離婚する
What?
え